surveyanyplace.com 2019-07-15

# Privacy Policy - Survey Anyplace

### Who we are

The website https://surveyanyplace.com/ (hereafter: the “Site”) is offered by:

OBJECTIVE7 BVBA (hereafter “SURVEY ANYPLACE”)  
Prins Boudewijnlaan 218A  
2650 Edegem  
Belgium  
VAT-BE 0845.741.317

E-mail us: [info@surveyanyplace.com ](mailto:info@surveyanyplace.com)

Support Center : [http://help.surveyanyplace.com](http://help.surveyanyplace.com/support/home)

Feel free to contact us should you have any privacy-related questions. We promise to reply soon!

### Why this Privacy Policy?

This privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) aims to inform you about how we use personal data collected via the Site. Please read this Privacy Policy before using the Site or submitting any personal data. This Privacy Policy supplements the SURVEY ANYPLACE Terms (and uses terms defined therein), and is a part of the agreement between SURVEY ANYPLACE and its Users.

Every person who visits the Site and/or registers (hereafter the “User” or “you”) discloses a certain amount of personal data. The personal data is information which allows SURVEY ANYPLACE to identify you as a natural person, regardless of whether we actually do this. You are identifiable as soon as it is possible to create a direct or indirect link between one or more data and you as a natural person.

SURVEY ANYPLACE is committed to the protection of the privacy of its Users, regardless of whether they are situated inside or outside the European Economic Area. We only use and process your personal data in accordance with the GDPR. The GDPR is short for the Regulation (EU) of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of individuals with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data (General Data Protection Regulation). This European regulation provides the highest level of privacy protection in the world. That is why we apply this high standard to all Users.

Through this Privacy Policy, every User of the Site is informed of the processing activities SURVEY ANYPLACE may carry out with his or her personal data. SURVEY ANYPLACE reserves the right to modify this Privacy Policy at all times. If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you by posting the new version of the Privacy Policy on the Site or may send each User a courtesy email. It is your responsibility to check the Site for updates to this Privacy Policy.

### Links to other websites

Our Site may contain or provide hyperlinks or pointed to other websites and/or electronic communication portals maintained by third parties or may provide third party content on our Site by framing or other methods. Such a reference being made on our Site does not mean that there is any connection between our Site and these third-party websites nor that we (implicitly) agree with the content on those sites.

We do not guarantee or assume any liability for the accuracy, legality, completeness or quality of the content of third-party websites linked to on our Site or of other electronic communications portals that are not under our actual control. These references are therefore to click at your own risk and responsibility. We are not liable for any damage resulting therefrom.

These external websites may not offer the same guarantees as we do. If you click on a link on this Site that leads to a foreign website and leaves your personal data on such a website, the processing of that personal data is not subject to this privacy policy, but to the privacy policy, if any, of the operator of that third-party website. We therefore recommend you to carefully read the terms and conditions and privacy statement of these other websites.

### Who is responsible for the processing of personal data?

#### Controller

SURVEY ANYPLACE is responsible for the processing of the personal data of the Users. SURVEY ANYPLACE decides alone or in cooperation with others which personal data are being collected as well as the purposes and the technical and organisational means with regard to the processing of those personal data.

SURVEY ANYPLACE has taken appropriate technical and organizational measures to protect the personal data of its Users. SURVEY ANYPLACE uses a variety of adequate security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. SURVEY ANYPLACE secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When financial information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to the payment gateway, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.

However, the User acknowledges that he acts in the capacity of data controller with regard to any personal data he uses or submits in or through a survey or other application or functionality of the Site, since the User decides alone which personal data of respondents are being collected, without interference from or control by SURVEY ANYPLACE. In this context, the User understands that SURVEY ANYPLACE acts as a mere processor. In that regard, User commits to communicate to its respondents that it relies on the services of an external processor who applies the same level of privacy standards as the User. In addition, we advise all Users to act in accordance with the GDPR by sufficiently informing all respondents of the purposes for which their personal data are collected and by obtaining the necessary consents.

#### Processor(s)

SURVEY ANYPLACE is free to rely on data processors. A processor is the natural or legal person who processes the personal data of the Users upon request and on behalf of the data controller. The processor is required to ensure the security and confidentiality of the data. The processor shall always act on the instructions of the data controller.

SURVEY ANYPLACE relies on the following categories of “processors”:

  * Companies we have engaged for hosting purposes (e.g. Amazon AWS);
  * Companies we have engaged for communication purposes (e.g. Intercom, MailChimp);
  * Companies we have engaged for administrative and billing purposes (e.g. Recurly, Freshbooks);

With a view to the optimal protection of the personal data of the Users, SURVEY ANYPLACE has made the necessary contractual arrangements with the aforementioned data processors to ensure that they apply the same standards as SURVEY ANYPLACE.

### On what legal grounds are my data processed?

In accordance with the GDPR we process personal data on the following legal grounds:

  * On the basis of the execution of the contract agreed upon with you or the execution of pre-contractual steps taken at your request; or
  * On the basis of compliance with legal or regulatory provisions with regard to the management of the contractual relationship, invoicing in particular;
  * On the basis of our legitimate interest in sending information and newsletters to our customers;
  * On the basis of your consent to send personalized marketing messages.

### Which personal data are being processed?

SURVEY ANYPLACE commits to only collect and process adequate, relevant and limited to what is necessary for the purposes for which they are processed. The following categories of personal data are processed by SURVEY ANYPLACE:

#### Non-paying customers:

  * Personal identification data (name (optional), first name, address, login details);
  * Contact details (email address)
  * Electronic identification data (IP address, cookies);

#### Paying customers:

  * Personal identification data (name, first name, address, login details);
  * Contact details (email address);
  * Financial identification data (credit card details);
  * Electronic identification data (IP address, cookies);

This data is collected at the time of your registration on the Site and when you use our services. Other personal data may be collected later, e.g. in the context of our after-sales. These data are necessary for the provision of SURVEY ANYPLACE services. The amount of personal data collected depends on your use of the Site and the functionalities of the Site.

### We also use cookies!

We also use cookies in order to recognise the User and to offer the returning User a personalised user experience, to remember technical choices, and to detect and correct any errors which might be present on the Site.

You remain free not to accept our cookies. For more information concerning the use of cookies, we kindly refer you to our [Cookie Statement](https://surveyanyplace.com/cookie-policy/).

### For which purposes are my personal data being used?

SURVEY ANYPLACE collects your personal data for the sole purpose of offering every User of our a safe, optimised and personal user experience of our Site and the offered services. The collection of personal data becomes more extensive as the User makes more intensive use of our Site and our online services. SURVEY ANYPLACE reserves the right to suspend or cancel certain operations if personal data is missing, incorrect or incomplete.

The processing of your personal data is essential for the proper functioning of the Site and the provision of associated services. SURVEY ANYPLACE commits to solely process your personal data for the following purposes:

  * Customer management: customer administration, user account management, subscription management, invoicing, support, complaint monitoring and sending newsletters.
  * Dispute management.
  * Protection against fraud and infringements.
  * For general advertising and marketing purposes (including audit, data analysis and research). SURVEY ANYPLACE may share demographic, profile and other general information about You and other Users with our partners on an aggregate basis.
  * Personalized marketing communication if you have expressly agreed to it. In that case, you are free to withdraw your consent at any time.

When visiting our Site, some data are being collected for statistical purposes. Such data is necessary to optimise your user experience. These data are: IP-address, probable location of consultation, hour and day of the consultation and the pages which are being consulted. When you visit the Site, you explicitly agree to this collection of data for statistical purposes.

The User provides the personal data to SURVEY ANYPLACE himself and can therefore exercise some kind of control. When certain data is incomplete or apparently incorrect, SURVEY ANYPLACE has the right to postpone some expected actions temporarily or permanently.

### Who receives your personal data?

Your personal data are processed for internal use within SURVEY ANYPLACE only. Your personal data will not be sold, passed on or communicated to any third parties, except in case you have given us your explicit prior consent.

If required to do so by law, regulation or under a good faith belief that action is necessary to conform to or comply with the law and legal process, to protect and defend SURVEY ANYPLACE rights and/or property and customers, whether or not required to do so by law. Survey Anyplace reserves the right to contact appropriate authorities and disclose personal data at its discretion when it appears that individuals are using the Site or services for illegal or infringing activities that otherwise violate the SURVEY ANYPLACE Privacy Policy or Terms.

We reserve the right to transfer and process your personal data on servers outside your country or outside the European Union or the European Economic Area. However, we will always do so in accordance with this Privacy Policy and the applicable laws.

In relation to a merger or acquisition by another company, or if the business unit providing Your service were sold to another company, personal data may be transferred to and used by the resulting combined company. If SURVEY ANYPLACE were to cease operations, this personal sata might be transferred to and used by another company, which offers similar or related products or services.

### How long do we store your personal data?

Your data is stored as long as necessary to achieve the ends pursued. They will be erased from our database as soon as they are no longer necessary for the ends pursued or if you validly exercise your right to erasure.

### What are my rights?

#### Guarantee of a legitimate and secure process of your personal data

Your personal data are always processed for the legitimate purposes explained in point 5. They are collected and processed in an appropriate, relevant and non-excessive manner, and are not kept longer than necessary to achieve the intended purposes.

#### Right to access

If you can prove your identity, you have the right to obtain information about the processing of your data. Thus, you have the right to know the purposes of the processing, the categories of data concerned, the categories of recipients to whom the data are transmitted, the criteria used to determine the data retention period, and the rights that you can exercise on your data.

#### Right to rectification of your personal data

Inaccurate or incomplete personal data may be corrected. It is primarily the responsibility of the User to make the necessary changes under “My Account” himself, but you can also request us in writing.

#### Right to erasure (or “right to be forgotten”)

You also have the right to obtain the erasure of your personal data under the following assumptions:

  * Your personal data are no longer necessary for the intended purposes;
  * You withdraw your consent to the processing and there is no other legal ground for processing;
  * You have validly exercised your right of opposition;
  * Your data has been illegally processed;
  * Your data must be deleted to comply with a legal obligation.

The deletion of data is mainly related to visibility; it is possible that the deleted data are still temporarily stored.

#### Right to limitation of processing

In certain cases, you have the right to request the limitation of the processing of your personal data, especially in case of dispute as to the accuracy of the data, if the data are necessary in the context of legal proceedings or the time required to SURVEY ANYPLACE to verify that you can validly exercise your right to erasure.

#### Right to object

You have the right to object at any time to the processing of your personal data for direct marketing purposes. SURVEY ANYPLACE will stop processing your personal data unless it can demonstrate that there are compelling legitimate reasons for the processing which prevail over your right to object.

#### Right to data portability

You have the right to obtain any personal data which you have provided us in a structured, commonly used and machine readable format. You are then free to transfer this data to a similar service provider.

#### Right to withdraw your consent

You may withdraw your consent to the processing of your personal data at any time, for example for personalized marketing communication purposes.

### How to exercise your rights?

If you wish to exercise your rights, you must send a written request and proof of identity by mail to SURVEY ANYPLACE, Prins Boudewijnlaan 218A, 2650 Edegem, Belgium or by email to [info@surveyanyplace.com](mailto:info@surveyanyplace.com).

We promise to respond as soon as possible, and no later than one (1) month after receipt of your request.

### Possibility to lodge a complaint

If you are not satisfied with the processing of your personal data by SURVEY ANYPLACE, you have the right to lodge a complaint with the competent Data Protection Authority (for Belgium: <https://www.privacycommission.be/>).

### Court of competent jurisdiction

In the event of any dispute regarding the execution or interpretation of this Privacy Policy, SURVEY ANYPLACE will do everything in its power to find an amicable solution. In the absence of an amicable solution, all disputes relating to or arising from the processing of personal data by SURVEY ANYPLACE will be submitted to the courts of the judicial district Antwerp.
